A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Administration, Building Services, Ford Foundation Headquarters, New Building Planning and Construction Files FA500
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Design and Planning, Bulk, 1963-1968 1951-1970 (bulk 1963-1968); 1963-1968; II (Box not specified)
  - Management Contractor -- Selection -- Draft Letters to Turner & Fuller, Jun 20, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Medical Area -- Notes, Jun 28, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Movable Partition System, Aug 10, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Move to New Building -- Informational Literature, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Move to New Building -- Proposals, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Nerva-Plast -- Product Information, Jan 25, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Nicely, J. M. -- Property Acquisition and Zoning, Feb 1963-Feb 1964 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Pamphlets and Brochures -- Visits to Other Buildings (1 of 2), [1957-1967] (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets and Brochures -- Visits to Other Buildings (2 of 2), [1957-1967] (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Parks Department -- Access Roads and Walks -- Correspondence Re: East Stairwell Exit with Background, Oct 1, 1964-May 10, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Parks Department -- Application -- Correspondence Re: Exit Door Easement, Permit, Pictures, Plans (See: Visual Images--Photos), Oct 28, 1964-Nov 3, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Personnel and Space Analysis -- Budgeted Positions -- Data and Lists, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Personnel and Space Analysis -- Economic Analysis of 320 E. 43rd Street -- Notes and Memorandum, Dec 8, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Personnel and Space Analysis -- Space Assignment, Jan 11, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Personnel and Space Analysis -- Telephone Systems -- Memoranda, Telephone Room Plans, Background, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Photostat Drawings -- 10A, 19, 23 and Elevation -- 321 East 43rd Street Erected 1911, Jun 11, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Planning and Designs -- Correspondence with Brookings Institute, etc. Re: Ford Foundation New Building Plans, Jan 7-Mar 27, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Planning Requirements -- Crowe, T.J., Apr 16-22, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Planning Requirements (1 of 2), Apr 22, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Planning Requirements (2 of 2), Apr 22, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Plumbing -- Jarcho Brothers -- Proposed Specifications (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Plumbing -- Jarcho Brothers -- Proposed Specifications (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Program Assignments -- Obsolete -- Floor Plans, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Property Purchase -- Plans for Hospital, Purchase of Berk Industries and Grand Central Hospital Closure, Deeds, Title Insurance, Mar 7, 1963-Apr 11, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Proposals -- Bid Documents (1 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Proposals -- Bid Documents (2 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Prospective Contractors -- Brochures (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Prospective Contractors -- Brochures (2 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Protection and Maintenance of Site -- Correspondence and Proposed Agreement Re: Security, Snow Removal, Jun 13, 1963-Dec 20, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Notifications -- Space for Rent Letters, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Reception Areas -- Notes Re: Design, UN Pass, Nov 24, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Rental Space -- 800 Second Avenue -- Sub-leases and Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Rezoning -- Notes, Oct 9, 1962-Jun 7, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Roche -- Ford Foundation Headquarters -- Addenda and Bulletins (1 of 3), Jul 1965 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Roche -- Ford Foundation Headquarters -- Addenda and Bulletins (2 of 3), Aug 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Roche -- Ford Foundation Headquarters -- Addenda and Bulletins (3 of 3), Dec 1965-Apr 1967 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Roche -- Ford Foundation Headquarters Specifications, May 3, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Roll-up Doors -- Kinnear Manufacturing Co -- Correspondence Re: Specification Approval, Feb 21-May 29, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Roof Storage -- Memorandum Re: Cancelling Plan, Feb 15, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Security -- Minutes and Memoranda Re: Security Plan, Nov 12, 1965-May 22, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Service Areas -- Notes and Memoranda, Jun 3, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Sewer -- Correspondence Re: Building Sewer Connection Design, Apr 22, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Shelter Area -- Memorandum, Correspondence and Background Re: Installing Civil Defense Area, Aug 25-Dec 10, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Shop Drawings -- Correspondence Re: Schedule, Dec 15, 1964-Oct 5, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Site Development -- Planning Requirements Cover Letters, Traffic Regulations, Nov 5, 1963-Sep 17, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Site Purchase -- Correspondence, Hospital Inventory, Copies of Deeds for Property and Purchase of Berk Industries, Mar 1, 1963-Feb 17, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Space Assignments -- Obsolete -- Plans, Details, Comments, etc., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Space Requirements -- Memoranda and Floor Plans, 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Special Areas -- Memoranda and Background Re: AV Design, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Staff Suggestions, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Staff Suggestions -- General -- Memoranda Re: Building Committee Meeting w/Architects, Aug 7, 1963-Feb 27, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Steam Supply System -- Correspondence with Consolidated Edison (Con Ed), Jan 26-Jun 4, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Storm Drainage System -- Memorandum Re: Cistern, Mar 10, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Storm, Sanitary Drains and Plumbing -- Requisition Request, Jun 28, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Structural -- Excavation and Foundations -- Inspection Report, Aug 26, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Structural -- "SK" Sketches, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Structural System -- Correspondence and Background Re: Steel Supports, Cor-Ten, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Structural Walls -- Memoranda and Background Re: Cor-Ten Steel, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Surveys -- Correspondence Re: Surveying, Easement Survey, Plans, Jun 4, 1963-Jun 18, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Surveys of Site -- Zoning Map, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Telephone System -- New York Telephone -- Proposal, Correspondence Re: Telephone Equipment Room, Plans (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Telephone System -- New York Telephone -- Memoranda and Plans Re: Centrex Cancellation (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Toilet Rooms -- Correspondence and Plans Re: Design, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- General Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Under-Surface Investigation -- Sub-surface Test Report, Jun 28-Dec 18, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Utilities and Building Operation, Sep 4, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Visits to and Notes Re: Other Buildings, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Western Gear -- Skyclimber -- Proposal and Design Stress Analysis, Aug 24, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Construction Files, Bulk, 1963-1969 1959-1971 (bulk 1963-1969); 1963-1969; III (Box not specified)
  Series III. Construction Files, 1959-1970 (bulk 1963-1969)
  This series holds files pertaining to the physical construction and assembly of the new headquarters building. Arranged in alphabetical order, the files contain meeting minutes and reports to the Trustees' Building Committee (1963-1970). Schedules, contracts, and building design meeting minutes regarding specific aspects of construction document the Turner Construction Company's operations as management contractor. Files about the design, installation and troubleshooting of the HVAC system are particularly extensive, as are reports created during the construction process. These include daily construction reports, as well as excavation reports, vibration studies, and structural steel analyses.
  - Acoustical Ceilings -- William J. Scully Acoustics Corp. -- Diagrams, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Acoustical Consultants -- Michael J. Kodaras, Inc., Jun 7, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Architects -- Field Memorandums, Jan 27, 1966-Jan 27, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Architects -- Field Orders, Feb 25, 1966-Jan 5, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Architects -- Finish Schedule, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Architects -- Luncheons with Architect and Management Contractor -- Agenda, Nov 19, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Architectural Metals -- General Bronze Corp. -- Correspondence Re: Specifications, Oct 11, 1966-Oct 3, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Architectural Metals -- J.W. Fiske -- Illustrations and Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Armor Elevators -- Sketches and Plans, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- Cost (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- Cost (2 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Authorizations and Directives -- Memoranda, Feb 18, 1964-Mar 3, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Acoustics -- Correspondence Re: Consulting, Jan 26, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Bidders and Quotations -- Various Trades, July 1965 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Boring -- Haller Testing Laboratories -- Blueprints, Bidding, Contract, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Building Audit -- Price Waterhouse, Mar 10, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Budget -- Budget, Monthly Cost Control Report, Cost Studies (1 of 2), 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Budget -- Cost Studies, Accounting Procedures, Status of Orders (2 of 2), 1964-1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Budget -- Miscellaneous Budget Lists and Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Budget -- Monthly Control Reports, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Building Enclosure -- American Bridge -- Contract, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Building Planning Committee -- Correspondence, General Data, Minutes (1 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Building Planning Committee -- Correspondence, General Data, Minutes (2 of 2), 1963-1967 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Bulletins, Agenda and Room Finish Schedules (1 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Bulletins, Agenda and Room Finish Schedules (2 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Ceramic Tiles -- Del Turco Brothers -- Correspondence Re: Tile Samples, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Changes, Alterations, Additions -- Memoranda, Floor Plans, Change Orders, Jan 31-Sep 24, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Charles Kurzon Inc. -- Keying Schedule, Plans, Background, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - C.I. Designs -- Correspondence Re: Billing Dispute with Invoices, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Computer -- Matrix Corporation -- Specifications, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Computerized Building Construction Control Network and Bar Chart, Feb 23, 1966-Jan 1, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Concrete Pours -- Daily Record, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Concrete Pours -- Sketches -- Floor Plans, [1966] (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Concrete Quality Supervision -- Robert Hunt & Co., 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Contractors -- Building Construction -- Proposals and Correspondence Re: Selection, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Contracts -- Dan Kiley, Casale & Nowell, Joseph N. Lacy, John V. Dinan, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Core Borings -- Severud-Elstad-Krueger-Assoc. -- Agreement and Memoranda, Jun 20, 1963-Dec 30, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Core Drilling -- Jersey Equipment and Tool, May 10, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Cosentini Associates -- Personnel Memoranda, 1959-1965 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cost Analysis -- Budget -- Monthly Reports with Memoranda, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Cost Analysis -- Building Construction Costs, Mar 1, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cost Analysis -- Classification of Building Construction Costs, Mar 1, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Cost Analysis -- Commercial Construction Cost Basis, Mar 1, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Cost Analysis -- Memoranda, Notes, Spreadsheets, etc., 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Cost Analysis -- Miscellaneous Work Sheets, 1965-1969 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Cost Analysis -- Monthly Control Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Cost Analysis -- Reasons for Changes in Costs to Sub-contracts, Mar 1, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Cost Analysis -- Sub-contractors to Turner Construction Co., Mar 1, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Cost Breakdown -- Exhibit A, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Critical Path Work Schedule -- Correspondence, Charts, Contract (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Critical Path Work Schedule -- Charts, Contract (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Demolition -- Letters to Bidders, Mar 6-Aug 7, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Demolition -- Lipsett Division -- Contract with Ford Foundation, Aug 6, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Detailed Analysis -- Additions to Contract Award, Jan 11, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Directives, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Electrical -- J. Livingston & Co. -- Electrical Generator, Diagram, Report, etc. (1 of 5), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Electrical -- J. Livingston & Co. -- Electrical Generator, Diagram, Report, etc. (2 of 5), 1965-1968 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Electrical -- J. Livingston & Co. -- Electrical Generator, Diagram, Report, etc. (3 of 5), 1965-1968 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Electrical -- J. Livingston & Co. -- Electrical Generator, Diagram, Report, etc. (4 of 5), 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Electrical -- J. Livingston & Co. -- Diagram and Report (5 of 5), [1969] (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Service (temporary) -- M. Eisenberg & Bros., Feb 2-Feb 5, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Excavation -- Boring Logs, Sep-Oct 1964 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Excavations and Foundations -- Sketches and Investigation Reports, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Grading and Backfill -- Anthony Muratore Contracting Co. -- Subcontract, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Elevators -- Armor Elevators -- Button Selection, May 10, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Finish Hardware -- Charles Kurzon Inc. (1 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Finish Hardware -- Charles Kurzon Inc. (2 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fire Protection -- Leeder Fire Protection Co., Dec 7, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Foundation -- T. Crimmins Contracting -- Minutes, Background, Sketches Re: Foundations, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Garden -- Main Garden and Plantings -- Dan Kiley -- Plans and Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1966 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Garage -- Memoranda and Plans, 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Glass and Glazing Work -- Samuel Kirschner & Sons Inc., 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Hardware -- Charles Kurzon -- Schedules (1 of 3), Feb 9, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Hardware -- Charles Kurzon -- Schedules (2 of 3), Apr 1-Oct 28, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Hardware -- Charles Kurzon -- Schedules (3 of 3), Dec 15, 1966-Aug 23, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Hardware -- Schedules for Movable Partitions, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Hermitage Wall Facing -- Specification, Dec 13, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Hoist Tower and Hoisting Equipment -- Heydt Contracting Corp., 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Hollow Metal Doors -- Firedoor Corp. -- Plans, May 19, 1966-Dec 5, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Hollow Metal Work -- Doors and Frames -- Firedoor Corp. of America -- Contract and Bidding, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Housing Administration Department of Buildings -- Application and Management Agreement, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - HVAC -- Barber Colman Co. -- Equipment Lists, Schedules, etc. (1 of 3), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - HVAC -- Barber Colman Co. -- Specifications (2 of 3), Jul 4-Aug 4, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - HVAC -- Barber Colman Co. -- Mixed-box Check (3 of 3), Jun 24, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - HVAC -- Color Code Chart, Nov 16, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - HVAC -- Conference Room and Board Room, Mar-Jun 1968 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - HVAC -- Cutler-Hammer -- Plans, Jan 6, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - HVAC -- Fans and Air Handlers, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - HVAC -- Havens -- Cooling Towers -- Plans, Nov 4, 1965-May 19, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Air Balancing Data (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Air Balancing Data (2 of 2), Dec 16, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Approval Drawings, Jun 22, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Chromalox, Feb 1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- General -- Thermostat Control Meeting, Costs, Problems, Billing, Minutes, Background, etc. (1 of 5), 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- General -- Punch Lists, etc. (2 of 5), 1965-1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- General -- Change Orders, Contract, Proposal, Bidding, etc. (3 of 5), 1965-1968 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- General -- Billing, Minutes (4 of 5), 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- General -- Minutes, Background (5 of 5), 1963-1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Submittal Data (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Submittal Data (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - HVAC -- Log of Job Activities -- Minutes, Jan 1969 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - HVAC -- Mechanical Systems -- Specifications and Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - HVAC -- Memoranda Re: HVAC System, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - HVAC -- Minutes, Memoranda, Invoices Re: HVAC, Plumbing, etc. (1 of 4), Nov 1965-Feb 1966 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - HVAC -- Minutes, Memoranda, Invoices Re: HVAC, Plumbing, etc. (2 of 4), Mar-Apr 1966 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - HVAC -- Minutes, Memoranda, Invoices Re: HVAC, Plumbing, etc. (3 of 4), May-Sep 1966 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - HVAC -- Minutes, Memoranda, Invoices Re: HVAC, Plumbing, etc. (4 of 4), Oct 1966-Mar 1967 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - HVAC -- National Sheet Metal -- Plans, Dec 2, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - HVAC -- Notes, Drawings, etc. (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - HVAC -- Notes, Drawings, etc. (2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - HVAC -- Temperatures in Building -- Studies on Equipment Performance, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - HVAC -- Total CFM -- Data and Plans, Jun 18, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - HVAC -- Trane, Feb 1968 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Iron Work -- Grossman Steel Stair Corp. -- Change Orders, Correspondence Re: Price, etc., 1965-1968 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - John Swenson Granite Co. -- Approval of Materials, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers -- Brochure, Apr 16, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Kitchen Equipment -- Straus Duparquet -- Book of Illustrations, Jun 9, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Kitchen Equipment -- Straus Duparquet -- Correspondence Re: Equipment Purchases, Third Party Litigation; Minutes, Contract, Change Orders, etc. (1 of 3), 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Kitchen Equipment -- Straus Duparquet -- Correspondence Re: Equipment Purchases, Third Party Litigation; Minutes, Contract, Change Orders, etc. (2 of 3), 1968 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Kitchen Equipment -- Straus Duparquet -- Correspondence Re: Equipment Purchases, Third Party Litigation; Minutes, Contract, Change Orders, etc. (3 of 3), 1968-1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Lighting -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Notes Re: Office and Street Lighting, 1964-1968 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Lipsett Division, Luria Bros. & Co., Inc. -- Contract with Ford Foundation, Dec 26, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Mail Conveyor -- Lamson Corp., Sep 8, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Management Committee Meeting -- Minutes, 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Management Contractor -- Procedures, Apr 16, 1964-Feb 28, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Masonry -- John B. Kelly Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Mechanical and Electrical -- Cosentini Associates -- Correspondence and Proposal Re: HVAC, etc., Aug 23, 1963-Feb 27, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Millwork and Carpentry -- Irving and Casson -- A.H. Davenport Co., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Mineral Tile Ceilings -- William J. Scully Acoustics Corp. -- Correspondence, Notes, Contracts, Mar 29, 1966-Aug 15, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Mirrors and Miscellaneous Glass -- Haber and Henry Inc., 1967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Movable Metal Partitions and Wall Liner -- Mills Company -- Change Orders, Contract, Bidding, Correspondence Re: Production Problems, Claims, Analysis (1 of 4), 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Movable Metal Partitions and Wall Liner -- Mills Company -- Change Orders, Contract, Bidding, Correspondence Re: Production Problems, Claims, Analysis (2 of 4), 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Movable Metal Partitions and Wall Liner -- Mills Company -- Change Orders, Contract, Bidding, Correspondence Re: Production Problems, Claims, Analysis (3 of 4), 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Movable Metal Partitions and Wall Liner -- Mills Company -- Change Orders, Contract, Bidding, Correspondence Re: Production Problems, Claims, Analysis (4 of 4), 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - New York City Building Codes -- Approved Amendments, Drawings, etc., Mar 29, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Operating and Maintenance -- Keying Schedule, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Ornamental Iron Work -- J.W. Fiske Architectural Metals -- Contract, Bidding, Change Orders, 1965-1968 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Painting, Miscellaneous Corrective -- Stuart-Dean Co., Inc. -- Contracts, Jun 21, 1967-May 22, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Painting Work -- J.I. Hass Co. Inc. -- Contracts, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Personnel -- Listing of Ford Foundation Officials and Organizational Chart, Nov 1963 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Photographs -- Mal Gurian Associates -- Contract, Insurance, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Piping -- Underground Piping "As Is" -- Drawings, Mar 28, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Planting Work -- Everett Conklin & Co., Inc. -- Correspondence and Notes Re: Estimate and Plant List (1 of 4), 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Planting Work -- Everett Conklin & Co. -- Interim Reports and Quotations, etc. (2 of 4), 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Planting Work -- Everett Conklin & Co. -- Contract, Correspondence Re: Quotes, Plant Types, etc. (3 of 4), 1965-1969 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Planting Work -- Everett Conklin & Co. -- Contract and Bidding (4 of 4), 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Planting Work -- Permit for Tree Planting, May 15, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Plumbing -- Jarcho Bros., Inc. -- Contract, Change Orders (1 of 3), 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Plumbing -- Jarcho Bros., Inc. -- Change Orders, Directives, Work Authorization (2 of 3), 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Plumbing -- Jarcho Bros., Inc. -- Bid, Proposal, Change Order (3 of 3), 1965-1967 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Plumbing System -- Correspondence Re: Directive and List, Oct 5, 1964-Mar 30, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Primary Power -- Consolidated Edison (Con Ed) -- Correspondence, Memoranda and Diagrams Re: Electric and Gas Supply, 1964-1967 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Procedures -- Correspondence and Memoranda, Sep 17, 1963-Feb 28, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Procedures and Approvals, Apr 15, 1964-Apr 20, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Punch List, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Reinforcing Steel Detailing -- Invoices, Aug 10, 1965-Feb 7, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Reports -- Areas Examined -- Park West and South Retaining Walls -- John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers, Mar 20, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Reports -- Building Committee -- Monthly Report -- Letters, Jun 12, 1963-Jan 18, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Reports -- Building Examined -- 328-334 East 43rd St. -- John V. Dinan, Mar 20, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Reports -- Building Examination -- 800 Second Avenue -- John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers (1 of 3), Mar 20, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Building Examination -- 800 Second Avenue -- John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers (2 of 3), Mar 20, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Building Examination -- 800 Second Avenue -- John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers (3 of 3), Mar 20, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 3)